export default data = [
  {
      question: "If we can ______ to, we will take a vacation abroad in the summer.",
      options: ["pay","move","expose","afford"],
      correct_option: "afford"
  },
  {
      question: "A ______ mistake found in parenthood is that parents often set unrealistic goals for their children.",
      options: ["terrific","common","straight","favorable"],
      correct_option: "common"
  },
  {
      question: "Some words, such as “sandwich” and “hamburger,” were ______ the names of people or even towns. ",
      options: ["originally","ideally","relatively","sincerely"],
      correct_option: "originally"
  },
  {
      question: "Have you ever ______ how the ancient Egyptians created such marvelous feats of engineering as the pyramids?",
      options: ["concluded","wondered","admitted","persuaded"],
      correct_option: "wondered"
  },
  {
      question: "Mr. Johnson was disappointed at his students for having a passive learning ______.",
      options: ["result","progress","attitude","energy"],
      correct_option: "attitude"
  },
  {
      question: "Anne dreaded giving a speech before three hundred people; even thinking about it made her ______.",
      options: ["passionate","anxious","ambitious","optimistic"],
      correct_option: "anxious"
  },
  {
      question: "I had to ______ Jack’s invitation to the party because it conflicted with an important business meeting.",
      options: ["decline","depart","devote","deserve"],
      correct_option: "decline"
  },
  {
      question: "Selling fried chicken at the night market doesn’t seem to be a decent business, but it is actually quite ______.",
      options: ["plentiful","precious","profitable","productive"],
      correct_option: "profitable"
  },
  {
      question: "The passengers ______ escaped death when a bomb exploded in the subway station, killing sixty people.",
      options: ["traditionally","valuably","loosely","narrowly"],
      correct_option: "narrowly"
  },
  {
      question: "Jerry didn’t ______ his primary school classmate Mary until he listened to her self-introduction.",
      options: ["acquaint","acquire","recognize","realize"],
      correct_option: "recognize"
  },
  {
      question: "With the completion of several public ______ projects, such as the MRT, commuting to work has become easier for people living in the suburbs.",
      options: ["transportation","traffic","travel","transfer"],
      correct_option: "transportation"
  },
  {
      question: "With a good ______ of both Chinese and English, Miss Lin was assigned the task of oral interpretation for the visiting American delegation.",
      options: ["writing","program","command","impression"],
      correct_option: "command"
  },
  {
      question: "I am studying so hard for the forthcoming entrance exam that I do not have the ______ of a free weekend to rest.",
      options: ["luxury","license","limitation","strength"],
      correct_option: "luxury"
  },
  {
      question: "Kim was completely ______ after jogging in the hot sun all afternoon; she had little energy left.",
      options: ["kicked out","handed out","worn out","put out"],
      correct_option: "worn out"
  },
  {
      question: "When Jason failed to pay his bill, the network company ______ his Internet connection.",
      options: ["cut off","cut back","cut short","cut down"],
      correct_option: "cut off"
  },
]
